<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release on Starcoin Developer</title><link>https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/tags/release/</link><description>Recent content in Release on Starcoin Developer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/tags/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starcoin Blockchain release v0.7</title><link>https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/news/post/release_starcoin_v0.7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/news/post/release_starcoin_v0.7/</guid><description>Starcoin Blockchain released v0.7, On the basis that the previous version has been running stably for more than a month, we continue to optimize the Chain, Consensus, Stdlib, Network and other modules to implement the CNR consensus algorithm, adjust the time accuracy, and improve the Spec verification coverage to more than 90%. Feel free to download Starcoin to join the Proxima test network for testing!</description></item><item><title>Starcoin Blockchain release v0.5</title><link>https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/news/post/release_starcoin_v0.5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/news/post/release_starcoin_v0.5/</guid><description>Starcoin Blockchain released v0.5, which is a major refactoring of the Block, Genesis, Stdlib modules, and implements the new Service Registry framework and adds a new Consensus Algorithm. The last version has been running stably for more than a month without deleting data, deployed six test nodes, and has reached more than 300,000 blocks of data. Feel free to download Starcoin to join the Proxima test network for testing!</description></item><item><title>Starcoin Blockchain release v0.4</title><link>https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/news/post/release_starcoin_v0.4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://starcoin-org.git.xin/en/news/post/release_starcoin_v0.4/</guid><description>Starcoin Blockchain releases v0.4, which includes refactoring and stabilization of basic types and protocols. One month after that, Starcoin Blockchain will start a month-long unabridged beta test. Feel free to download Starcoin and join the Proxima test network.</description></item></channel></rss>